Abductions on Bedford Road this time. You're certain?
Upon my word as a thief, Captain.
They's taking beggars and tramps right off the streets, just like you said.
Then I fear the worst Jacobs,
for only men of influence might sanction such blatant mischief.
and the captors were taken to an inn you say?
Somewhere thereabouts, The Hare in the Snare they calls it, and that's where I've gone with my infestation.
Investigation.
That's what I said!
Ah, anyway, I've taken a room at the inn, gonna start sniffing about.
No, I shall not endanger you any further.
These abductions no doubt serve the interests of a greater corruption,
or else I'd not have been ordered to turn a blind eye.
If the City watch is in on it, then you need my help.
And you promised me the job, Captain.
(sighs) Sneaking about the inn will place you in great danger, Jacobs.
I'm a thief. Sneakin's the one thing I'm almost good at.
I don't like it, but I am left with few choices.
My hands are tied, and I suppose you have proven your worth.
That's right. And if I fail, you need only find my old mate at this address.
He's a right fox him, he'll get it done.
And he's got a special talent for all of them things what you shall not approve of.
Then let us hope I have no need of his talents.
Paying one of you is quite enough.
Well, I better head back before they close for the night.
And don't you worry, Captain. I'll find out what's going on
and they will never suspect a thing.
A letter at this hour.
Curious.